So if you pull down 08 exercise, you'll
be able to see all the code that I just did.
I want you to go ahead on your own app,
create your own base layout, play around in slots,
see how you might want to rearrange things,
see how that feels when you have one slot
versus having multiple slots with name slots.
All right, how did everyone feel about playing around
with slots?
Good, fairly straightforward.
That is great to hear.
OK, so what I'm going to do is just basically
I'm going to take a look at the ATL LA forum on my end,
and we'll just do a quick one as far as that goes.
So let me go ahead and check out a branch.
Oh wait, solution, CD ATLA, great, run dev.
Everything should be running as expected.
Yep, perfect, OK.
So when I'm looking at ATLA, I'm thinking, OK,
well, base component, what does the base layout look like?
So I'm going to go ahead, create my base layout,
dot view.
Inside of here, let's keep it simple.
So we're just going to have the template,
and all that it manages is where things are placed.
So we'll actually just create basically
as to how many things we have, four things.
All right, so let's do a div, and then we'll have here,
so we'll call this class grid.
And then we'll say, do, do, do, do.
Actually, this time we'll open the style block.
And for grid, we'll display grid and grid template columns
to repeat 2, 1, FR.
Basically, this will repeat two columns inside of this.
So div and div.
And then for now, let's just go ahead and drop this
to make this a slot.
And then we'll say the name for this slot is 1.
This will be the first one.
And then we'll copy this.
And then just drop it in here for 2.
Autocomplete.
Just slot.
Thank you for catching that.
OK, inside of our app, we're going to go ahead, grab that.
And then this will be base layout.
Go ahead and copy that.
Base layout.
Then we'll actually call it here.
And this time in base layout, we'll go ahead and let's take
our new character down here.
I think that's all of this stuff.
And then let's just drop that in the first slot to start.
So where are we here?
So we'll have the template here dropping in the new character.
And the vslot we're looking for is 1.
So if you save that, you'll see that we're actually, I guess
let me show this so that it's a little bit clearer.
Pi, Pi, Solid, Green.
Actually, what's a fun?
But Pyowit, I love that one.
Let's do it.
OK, not very accessible, though.
I like the name.
OK, so we can see here that that is showing up on the left
hand side.
And then all we need to do, if you want to swap it, for
example, is just do vslot2.
And you can see it jumps from left to right.
And so that's just like a simple implementation of a
possible grid.
And you can imagine when you start combining these with
CSS, slotting stuff around, you get some pretty powerful
stuff when it comes to responsive design as well.